mahindraxuv500.com 2015-04-07

# Mahindra XUV500 | SUV India | SUVs Cars | Luxury SUV | SUV in India 2011 | The best suv | Top suv in india | New suv in india

We collect information about you when you visit our site, use our services, or view our online advertisements. The information which we collect and store during normal use of the site is used to monitor use of the site and to help further development of our products and services. In general you can visit Mahindra XUV500 website on the Internet without telling us who you are or providing data that personally identifies you. Such use does not result in any personally identifiable data being collected or stored.

## Privacy Statement

Protecting your privacy and ensuring that your personal data is held securely is very important to Mahindra XUV500. We want you to be confident that we are looking after your interests and that is why we have set out our information practices in this Privacy Statement.

We do not share your information with third parties, unless we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested and we have asked for and obtained your explicit consent. The foregoing notwithstanding, if (1) disclosure was required by law, rule or regulation or was in response to a valid order of a court or authorized agency of government or other legal process and/or; (2) When we find your action on the web site violates the Mahindra XUV500 terms and condition or any of your usage guidelines for specific products or services.

This Privacy Statement will apply when you use our website to discover more information about Mahindra XUV500 and its products. This Privacy Statement is applicable to data collected by Mahindra XUV500 and other Mahindra XUV500 companies worldwide for use by these companies.

Whilst any application, request or enquiry you make, may be passed or made available to Mahindra XUV500 affiliates some of which will be based in countries that do not have data protection laws, all Mahindra XUV500 affiliates are required to comply with an internal Privacy Policy which requires that steps are taken to protect your Personal Data and for it only to be used for the purpose(s) for which it was submitted.

By submitting your Personal Data through this website, you shall be consenting to it being processed in the manner described above by Mahindra XUV500 affiliates around the world and our hosting organizations around the world.
